<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Our Blog on Organic Food Incubator</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Our Blog on Organic Food Incubator</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How To Develop A Brand For Food And Beverage Startup Businesses</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/how-to-develop-a-brand-for-food-and-beverage-startup-businesses/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/how-to-develop-a-brand-for-food-and-beverage-startup-businesses/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A food and beverage startup can be very lucrative. But it’s not easy, so you&#xA;need to make sure you get your branding right.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4 Benefits Of Having an Organic Food Certified Product</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/4-benefits-of-having-an-organic-food-certified-product/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/4-benefits-of-having-an-organic-food-certified-product/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You just got your new product finished, you got your Scheduled Process, and now&#xA;you’re ready to get your product to mainstream markets and supermarkets. But&#xA;then your wondering should you get your product organic food certified or not.&#xA;But let me tell you this first, not all products need an organic food&#xA;certification. You have to use your best judgment. To decide that question first&#xA;we need to talk about some of the benefits of having an organic food-certified&#xA;product will provide.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What Is A Scheduled Process?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/what-is-a-scheduled-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/what-is-a-scheduled-process/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You just came up with a brand new product. Now, you want to get it distributed&#xA;and produced on a large scale to send out to stores. Before you can do that you&#xA;need to determine if you need to get a scheduled process completed and if you do&#xA;need one, complete it. Most beverages, sauces, and condiments need a scheduled&#xA;process. What is a scheduled process?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Intro To Product Shelf Life Stability And Acidity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/intro-to-product-shelf-life-stability-and-acidity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/intro-to-product-shelf-life-stability-and-acidity/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For many products, acidity is a very important aspect of development, as it can&#xA;help ensure shelf life stability. In small batches of food manufacturing, pH is&#xA;a critical factor enabling your product to be shelf-stable. pH is important for&#xA;food items as pathogenic bacteria cannot grow in a low pH environment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is It Important To Be Certified Organic Or Kosher?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/is-it-important-to-be-certified-organic-or-kosher/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/is-it-important-to-be-certified-organic-or-kosher/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Is it important to be certified organic or kosher? Both of these certifications&#xA;have benefits but are often costly, so they are not suitable for all products.&#xA;However, having these certifications may open your product to new markets.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who Is My Target Market? A Product Marketing Tip</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/who-is-my-target-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/who-is-my-target-market/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Who is my target market? Identifying your target market is a crucial step in&#xA;creating a successful product. Often people producing a product will say that&#xA;their product is for everyone, but that is a mistake! Many different consumer&#xA;bases may purchase your product, but you will have a few core target markets or&#xA;target audiences that make up the bulk of your purchases. So–how do you figure&#xA;out who your target market is?&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Where To Start? How To Start Producing And Selling Your Product!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/where-to-start-how-to-start-producing-and-selling-your-product/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/where-to-start-how-to-start-producing-and-selling-your-product/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;You have an incredible product that you want to produce and sell. We would love&#xA;to help–but before we do, here are some steps to streamline the process.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Margins And Costs | Where Is Your Profit?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/margins-and-costs-where-is-your-profit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/margins-and-costs-where-is-your-profit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When we are talking about margins and costs relating to the food manufacturing&#xA;industry, you need to know some basic information. Perhaps the most important&#xA;information is what portion of the money earned from your product you’ll&#xA;actually be making!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Business Tip: Pretend You&#39;re Bigger Than You Are</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/business-tip-pretend-you-are-bigger-than-you-are/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/business-tip-pretend-you-are-bigger-than-you-are/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just like meeting a person for the first time, businesses often make judgments&#xA;on first impressions. Here’s a business tip that you might want to consider-&#xA;pretend you’re bigger than you are.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Food Shelf Stability and Expiration?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/what-is-food-shelf-stability-and-expiration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/what-is-food-shelf-stability-and-expiration/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Most products that OFI produces are shelf-stable, meaning that they do not need&#xA;to be refrigerated, and must be subjected to heat treatment to prevent the&#xA;growth of pathogens, primarily botulism. This heat treatment can offer shelf&#xA;stability for a long time.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Filing a Scheduled Process</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/filing-a-scheduled-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/filing-a-scheduled-process/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For most shelf-stable fluid products, it is necessary to obtain a scheduled&#xA;process prior to producing the product.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;A scheduled process is your recipe and procedure, which has been reviewed and&#xA;edited by a recognized process authority. With very few exceptions, if you are&#xA;making a product that is fluid and shelf-stable, you will be required to have a&#xA;scheduled process.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
